(Raj:)-Since when?
-I'll show you a picture...
(Howard:)...of my Uncle Louie
in a bathing suit sometime.
(Howard:)Leonard, you gotta see this.
We found a match for Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Great. Maybe she can have sex with him
and walk out on him the next morning...
(Leonard:)...without so much
as a "How do you do?"
(Raj:)-Know what he's talking about?
-No. Ask him.
-Leonard, what?
-I don't wanna talk about it.
(Raj:)That was a lousy suggestion.
(Howard:)Whatever.
(Howard:)Right now, Dr. Sheldon Cooper
has to send an e-mail to his perfect match.
"Greetings, fellow life-form...."
(Leonard:)If she can do it, I can do it.
If she can do it, I can do it.
(Leonard:)I can't do it.
(Leslie Winkle:)-Hello?
-Oh, hi. Hey.
(Leonard:)Hi, Leslie.
Leonard, what're you doing here?
I know. It's been a while.
(Leslie:)Yeah, 18 months.
(Leonard:)Right. Right.